>> Jem Young: 好的， Nginx 为我们提供了一个页面。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right,
Nginx is serving us a page.
但那是从哪里来的
But where did that come from?
它在干什么
What is it doing?
我们来看看吧
Let's take a look.
那么，让我们看看 Nginx 的配置。
So, let's look at the Nginx configuration.
而且我们要花很多钱
And we're gonna spend a lot of, well,
我们要花一段时间在 Nginx 的配置中
we're gonna spend a fair amount of
time in the Nginx configuration.
那就让我们熟悉吧
So, let's get familiar with it.
所以你要做的是什么 ?
So, sudo less or vi or cat or
whatever you want to do,
但在不那么多的 Nginx 网站上
but up for
less etc Nginx sites available and
我们将使用缺省配置。
we're going to use
the default configuration.
记住你可以完成大部分的工作
And remember you can tab
complete most of this.
所以我想说的是更少的 nginx 网站
So I will say sudo less
etc nginx sites-available,
和你的默认值
and default, cool, and
有很多我知道这很多
it's a lot, I know it's a lot.
Nginx 请在此处提供注释，链接以开始阅读。
Nginx kindly provides comments in here,
links to start reading.
我现在警告你 Nginx 文件不好看
I'll warn you now the Nginx
documentation is not pretty.
太好了 很明显很彻底
It's good.
It's thorough, obviously,
但这不是你能理解的最可读性的东西
but it's not the most readable thing
you're ever going to run across.
所以一般来说，如果你说的是微调 Nginx ，最好是做谷歌
So generally, if you're talking about
tweaking Nginx, it's better to do Google
搜索它并在一个博客上读到一篇关于它的文章。
search on it and read a blog post
on somebody that's talked about it.
几乎所有事都想在内克斯之前做过
Almost everything want to do in
Nginx someone has done before.
所以这是最好的方法。
So that's a better way to go.
但是如果你真的想读博士
However, if you really want to,
read the docs.
我不推荐这个
I don't recommend it.
你也可以用这个男人的页面，我也不推荐。
You can also use the man page,
I don't recommend that either.
但如果你需要它就在那里
[LAUGH] But it's there if you need it.
我们一会儿再谈这个
And we'll talk more
about that in a second.
>> Jem Young: 所以在 Nginx 的配置下，有很多不同的事情，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So with Nginx configuration
there's a lot of different things,
我今天要强调一下
I'm gonna try to highlight them today.
贝司目录
The bass directory for
所有请求都将转至斜杠 dub dub dub HTML 。
all requests are going to go to
slash var dub dub dub slash HTML.
缺省情况下，所有请求都将进入该位置。
That's where all requests
are going to go by default.
我们要把这个目录保存在
And we're going to keep that
directory cuz it's just
好地方把你的东西都留着
the nice place to keep all your web stuff.
如果需要，可以移动，但斜杠 " dub dub dub " 为
You can move around if you want,
but slash var slash dub dub dub is
通常人们把大部分的应用和东西都保留在那里
usually where people keep most of their
applications and things like that.
但你可以把它移到你想要的地方
But you can move it to wherever you want.
一个定位块就是为了
A location block is just saying for
每一个进入服务器的请求，我该怎么办?
every request that comes into the server,
what should I do?
还有这里的 Nginx 正则表达式
And Nginx regular expressions here,
在这件事上它只是把一切都准备好了
in this case it's just slash it's
gonna match everything coming in.
它会尝试为这个文件服务所以它会为其中一个提供服务
It's gonna try to serve the file,
so it's gonna serve one of these.
如果没有，就会有 404 页面。
And if it doesn't,
it's just gonna 404 page.
我们要用这个位置块
We're gonna use the location
blocks slash for
我们今天要做的事
most of the things we're gonna do today.
我们不会创建路径或子域之类的。
We're not gonna create paths or
subdomains or things like that.
但这只是个定位块
But that's just called a location block.
这一尝试强调了文件，这是 Nginx的一个指令。
This try underscore files,
it's what's known as a directive in Nginx.
本质上，它是一个叫做宏做某件事的宏观方法。
Essentially, it's a called a macro for
doing something.
我们待会儿要用的是代理过去
The one we're gonna use a little bit later
is proxy past which we'll talk about.
这会将您的请求代理到服务器的其他部分。
And that's gonna proxy your request
to some other part of the server.
但是尝试文件意味着它会尝试查找其中一个文件。
But try files just means it's gonna
try to look up one of these files.
如果它不可能的话就会有 404 页
And if it can't any of them,
it's gonna 404 page.
会说错误的对吧
It's gonna say error, right?
现在，我们在 Nginx 配置中有一个服务器块。
So here we are, we have a server
block in Nginx configuration.
它是缺省服务器，所以它在端口 80上列出。
It's a default server, so
it's listing on port 80.
所有这些东西都在那儿
All this stuff's there.
有一个根目录，服务器名称，稍后我们会更改，
There's a root directory, the server name,
which we'll change later,
但现在我们不需要因为它是默认的服务器
but for now we don't need to
because it's the default server
仍然接受来自各地的联系
still accepting connections
from everywhere.
这里有个定位块
Here's a location block.
现在您可以忽略其他部分。
You can ignore the rest of this for now.
这是您的 Nginx 配置。
This is your Nginx configuration.
所以，让我们微调一下，不要再 q了。
So let's tweak it a little bit and
quit just q.
所以现在，这个默认页面是来自神奇的神秘土地。
So for now, that default page
came out of magic mystery land.
我们开始创建一个，然后编辑它以更改为您想要的任何内容。
Let's go and create one and then edit
it to change to whatever you want.
它将更改缺省页面，因为这样您就知道您的目录
It's going to change the default page
because that way you know your directories
正在工作，并且文件正在运行，并且正在正常工作。
are working, and the files are working,
and it's serving correctly.
因此， sudo vi/var/www/html ，然后创建 index.html 页面。
So, sudo vi/var/www/html and
then create an index.html page.
所以，我要在这里做。
So, I'm going to go ahead and
do that here.
须多
Sudo
> > Jem Young: 我知道你在想什么不是合适的 HTML ，不重要。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I know what you're thinking
that's not proper HTML, doesn't matter.
会有效的
It will work.
如果我想做什么喜欢造型的东西就会坏了
If I try to do anything fancy,
like styling, it's gonna break.
但现在，你不用写一个完整的 HTML 页面。
But for now, you don't have
to write an entire HTML page.
如果我们有更多的时间，我想说谁能在 10 分钟内创造最佳的 HTML 页面。
If we had more time, I'd say who can
create the best HTML page in 10 minutes.
我觉得我比你还糟
And I feel bad cuz I beat you.
所以，我开玩笑的，我不会的，这不是我的福手。
So, I'm kidding, I wouldn't,
that is not my forte.
这就是我的专长领域。
This is more my area of expertise.
但是我们要去 wq
But we're just going to wq that and
when we
在我们现在有另一个页面之前刷新我们的页面，因为
refresh our page before we now have a
different page because instead of looking
在默认的 Nginx 页面上，在索引点 HTML 中的顺序是有序的。
to that default Nginx page, it's looking
in order in index dot HTML comes in order.
到目前为止所有人都来了吗
Everybody here so far?
太酷了
Cool.
现在我们正在做一些事情，我们现在正在为自己的服务器提供一个 HTML 页面。
Now we're doing something, we are now
serving an HTML page on our own server.
我知道些什么
I know little things.
我觉得很酷
I think it's cool.
干得好
Good job.